[
    {
        "front": "军",
        "back": "army, military; soldiers, troops",
        "pronunciation": "jūn",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "战",
        "back": "war, fighting, battle",
        "pronunciation": "zhàn",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "政",
        "back": "government, political affairs",
        "pronunciation": "zhèng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "产",
        "back": "give birth, bring forth, produce",
        "pronunciation": "chǎn",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "制",
        "back": "system; establish; overpower",
        "pronunciation": "zhì",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "代",
        "back": "replace, replacement (of person or generation); era, generation",
        "pronunciation": "dài",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "立",
        "back": "stand; let stand; establish, set",
        "pronunciation": "lì",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "义",
        "back": "right conduct, righteousness",
        "pronunciation": "yì",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "神",
        "back": "spirit, god, supernatural being",
        "pronunciation": "shén",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "德",
        "back": "ethics, morality, virtue",
        "pronunciation": "dé",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "统",
        "back": "govern, command, control; unite",
        "pronunciation": "tǒng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "形",
        "back": "form, shape, appearance",
        "pronunciation": "xíng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "治",
        "back": "govern, regulate, administer",
        "pronunciation": "zhì",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "达",
        "back": "arrive at, reach; intelligent; smooth, slippery",
        "pronunciation": "dá",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "强",
        "back": "strong, powerful, energetic",
        "pronunciation": "qiáng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "权",
        "back": "power, right, authority",
        "pronunciation": "quán",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "王",
        "back": "king, ruler; royal; surname",
        "pronunciation": "wáng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "设",
        "back": "build; establish; display",
        "pronunciation": "shè",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "品",
        "back": "article, product, commodity",
        "pronunciation": "pǐn",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "类",
        "back": "class, group, kind, category",
        "pronunciation": "lèi",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "领",
        "back": "neck; collar; lead, guide",
        "pronunciation": "lǐng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "造",
        "back": "construct, build, make, begin; prepare",
        "pronunciation": "zào",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "组",
        "back": "class; section, department",
        "pronunciation": "zǔ",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "英",
        "back": "petal, flower, leaf; brave, a hero; England, English",
        "pronunciation": "yīng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "令",
        "back": "",
        "pronunciation": "lìng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "布",
        "back": "cotton cloth, textiles, linen",
        "pronunciation": "bù",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "未",
        "back": "not yet; 8th terrestrial branch",
        "pronunciation": "wèi",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "击",
        "back": "strike, hit, beat; attack, fight",
        "pronunciation": "jī",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "兵",
        "back": "soldier, troops",
        "pronunciation": "bīng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "团",
        "back": "sphere, ball, circle; mass, lump",
        "pronunciation": "tuán",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "集",
        "back": "assemble, collect together",
        "pronunciation": "jí",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "华",
        "back": "flowery; illustrious; Chinese",
        "pronunciation": "huá",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "石",
        "back": "stone, rock, mineral; rad. 112",
        "pronunciation": "shí",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "府",
        "back": "prefecture; prefect; government",
        "pronunciation": "fǔ",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "似",
        "back": "resemble, similar to; as if, seem",
        "pronunciation": "shì",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "官",
        "back": "official, public servant",
        "pronunciation": "guān",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "器",
        "back": "receptacle, vessel; instrument",
        "pronunciation": "qì",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "称",
        "back": "call; name, brand; address; say",
        "pronunciation": "chēng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "企",
        "back": "plan a project; stand on tiptoe",
        "pronunciation": "qǐ",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "委",
        "back": "appoint, send, commission",
        "pronunciation": "wěi",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "曾",
        "back": "already; sign of past",
        "pronunciation": "céng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "农",
        "back": "agriculture, farming; farmer",
        "pronunciation": "nóng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "装",
        "back": "dress, clothes, attire; fill",
        "pronunciation": "zhuāng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "显",
        "back": "manifest, display; evident, clear",
        "pronunciation": "xiǎn",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "念",
        "back": "think of, recall, study",
        "pronunciation": "niàn",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "青",
        "back": "blue, green, black; young",
        "pronunciation": "qīng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "武",
        "back": "military; martial, warlike",
        "pronunciation": "wǔ",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "势",
        "back": "power, force; tendency",
        "pronunciation": "shì",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "古",
        "back": "old, classic, ancient",
        "pronunciation": "gǔ",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "构",
        "back": "frame, building, structure",
        "pronunciation": "gòu",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "土",
        "back": "soil, earth; items made of earth",
        "pronunciation": "tǔ",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "投",
        "back": "throw, cast, fling, pitch; jump",
        "pronunciation": "tóu",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "某",
        "back": "certain thing or person",
        "pronunciation": "mǒu",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "维",
        "back": "maintain, preserve, safeguard",
        "pronunciation": "wéi",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "革",
        "back": "leather, animal hides; rad. 177",
        "pronunciation": "gé",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "敌",
        "back": "enemy, foe, rival; resist",
        "pronunciation": "dí",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "致",
        "back": "send, deliver, present; cause",
        "pronunciation": "zhì",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "派",
        "back": "school of thought, sect, branch",
        "pronunciation": "pài",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "营",
        "back": "encampment, barracks; manage",
        "pronunciation": "yíng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "巴",
        "back": "greatly desire, anxiously hope",
        "pronunciation": "bā",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "防",
        "back": "defend; prevent; embankment",
        "pronunciation": "fáng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "施",
        "back": "grant, bestow; give; act; name",
        "pronunciation": "shī",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "型",
        "back": "pattern, model, type; law; mold",
        "pronunciation": "xíng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "依",
        "back": "rely on, be set in; consent, obey a wish",
        "pronunciation": "yī",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "群",
        "back": "(same as羣) group, crowd, multitude, mob",
        "pronunciation": "qún",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "项",
        "back": "neck, nape of neck; sum; funds",
        "pronunciation": "xiàng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "织",
        "back": "weave, knit; organize, unite",
        "pronunciation": "zhī",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "斗",
        "back": "Chinese peck; liquid measure",
        "pronunciation": "dòu",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "采",
        "back": "collect, gather; pick, pluck",
        "pronunciation": "cǎi",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "杀",
        "back": "kill, slaughter, murder; hurt",
        "pronunciation": "shā",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "朝",
        "back": "dynasty; morning",
        "pronunciation": "cháo",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "属",
        "back": "class, category, type; belong to",
        "pronunciation": "shǔ",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "限",
        "back": "boundary, limit, line",
        "pronunciation": "xiàn",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "威",
        "back": "pomp, power; powerful; dominate",
        "pronunciation": "wēi",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "状",
        "back": "form; appearance; shape; official",
        "pronunciation": "zhuàng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "率",
        "back": "to lead; ratio; rate; limit",
        "pronunciation": "lǜ",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "独",
        "back": "alone, single, solitary, only",
        "pronunciation": "dú",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "创",
        "back": "establish, create; knife cut",
        "pronunciation": "chuàng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "承",
        "back": "inherit, receive; succeed",
        "pronunciation": "chéng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "股",
        "back": "thighs, haunches, rump; share",
        "pronunciation": "gǔ",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "益",
        "back": "profit, benefit; advantage",
        "pronunciation": "yì",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "血",
        "back": "blood; radical number 143",
        "pronunciation": "xuè",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "素",
        "back": "white (silk); plain; vegetarian; formerly; normally",
        "pronunciation": "sù",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "夜",
        "back": "night, dark; in night; by night",
        "pronunciation": "yè",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "初",
        "back": "beginning, initial, primary",
        "pronunciation": "chū",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "源",
        "back": "spring; source, head; surname",
        "pronunciation": "yuán",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "食",
        "back": "eat; meal; food; KangXi radical number 184",
        "pronunciation": "shí",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "待",
        "back": "treat, entertain, receive; wait",
        "pronunciation": "dài",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "述",
        "back": "narrate, state, express",
        "pronunciation": "shù",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "陆",
        "back": "land, continental; army",
        "pronunciation": "lù",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "置",
        "back": "place, lay out; set aside",
        "pronunciation": "zhì",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "劳",
        "back": "labor, toil, do manual work",
        "pronunciation": "láo",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "财",
        "back": "wealth, valuables, riches",
        "pronunciation": "cái",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "纳",
        "back": "admit, take, receive, accept",
        "pronunciation": "nà",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "雷",
        "back": "thunder",
        "pronunciation": "léi",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "模",
        "back": "model, standard, pattern; copy",
        "pronunciation": "mó",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "充",
        "back": "fill, be full, supply",
        "pronunciation": "chōng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "木",
        "back": "tree; wood, lumber; wooden",
        "pronunciation": "mù",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "龙",
        "back": "dragon; symbolic of emperor",
        "pronunciation": "lóng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    },
    {
        "front": "冲",
        "back": "soar; pour boiling water over",
        "pronunciation": "chōng",
        "collection_id": "5"
    }
]